Carni Klirs PUNK005
People's Archive, MLK Library
Carni Klirs Collection
2002-2009
People's Archive, MLK Library
Klirs, Carni
PUNK005
3 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1: Printed Materials
  - Subseries 1: Fliers - Concerts - DC Venues
    - A-L, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - M-Z, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alfishaway Cafe / People's Media Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American University / Kay Spiritual Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bervin Haus / Bervin House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Black Cat, The, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bobby Fisher Memorial Building, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Brian Mackenzie Infoshop, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Casa, La, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Electric Maid, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Eternal Life, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Flemming Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Fort Reno, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Girl Cave, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Not a Squat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Pinch, The, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - St. Aloysius, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - St, Stephens, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Velvet Lounge, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Warehouse Next Door, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2: Fliers - Concerts - MD Venues
    - Brothel House, The - Kensington, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Corpse Fortress - Silver Spring, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Deathstar - Silver Spring, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fort Posi - College Park, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Jenkin's Church - Pasadena, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - North Chevy Chase Rec Center - Chevy Chase, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Ottobar - Baltimore, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Nowarehouse - Baltimore, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Talking Head, The - Baltimore, MD, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Treeswing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - University of Maryland, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 3: Fliers- Concerts - VA Venues
    - 15600 Buck Lane - Montclair, VA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - George Mason University, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Kansas House - Arlington, VA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Murky Coffee - Arlington, VA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 4: Fliers - Festivals - DC
    - Different Kind of Dude Fest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Positive Youth Fest - Warehouse Theater, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 5: Fliers - Festivals - MD
    - Really Really Free Market, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Series 2: Objects
  - Patches and Stickers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Series 3: Audio-Visual Material
  - Subseries 1: Cassettes
    - 2007 European Tape by Anchors (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes booklet with song lyrics, housed in a cardboard box
    - The Author by Bear and the Butterfly, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Labeled "Tape of '05 (summer)"
    - BxB by Bear and the Butterfly, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Includes small zine with drawings, collage, housed in cardboard box
    - Boost Fine Lines Split by Boost/Fine Lines, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Contains lyrics sheet
    - Hey Girl by Hey Girl, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hot Mess by Hot Mess, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Contains lyrics sheet, containede in cloth pouch
    - Tryangle by Ingrid (Label: Cosmis Debris), 2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Contains art insert
    - Hey Fragile by Lava Lava, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Contains Lyrics sheet, collage
    - Mass Movement of the Moth by Mass Movement of the Moth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Transgression by Transgression, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Order of the Turboslut by Turboslut, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Contains lyric sheet, collage
  - Subseries 2: CDs
    - 4 song demo by 1905, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ab by Alcian Blue (Label: Safranin Sounds), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - An Alarm by An Alarm (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Cased with lyrics sheet in cardboard sheetes
    - There are murderers on your thrones by Attentat, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Contains zine
    - Preface by Attrition, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Barkitecture Quarry by Bark (Label: J Streeet Records), 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Bazhena by Bazhena, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Nine times! by Chugga Chugga, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Demo March 2004 by Del Cielo (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Et At It by Et At It, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - [demo]lition by Gurth (Box 3, Folder 11)
      contains lyrics sheet
    - Haram by Haram, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 4567 by Horses, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - every day i have more to fear but less to lose by How We Tie Knots, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      contains zine
    - Lois Lame by Lois Lame, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Owned EP by Magrudergrind, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Medic by Medic, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
      contains numbered lyrics sheet
    - Polar Demo 2005 by Polar (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - X-Polynation by Q and Not U (Label: Dischord Records), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Sampler by Riot Folk! (Label: Riot Folk), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Songs of August Demo CD by Songs of August, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - time of the wolf by time of the wolf, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)